Here's how Push A flipped Ghostface
Killer's famous gold cuff into a
brilliant triple on tandrace.
[music]
The only driven by
ghost face with the wrist bird falcon.
[music]
>> Push plays on Saudi Arabia's majority
desert landscape which matches his tan
Rolls-Royce. This Saudi reference sets
up the triple entandra. Ghostface with
the wrist bird falcon which first refers
to Ghostface Killer's golden cuff that
features a landing eagle that sits on
his wrist. The image is similar to a
falconer, someone who trains and hunts
with birds of prey. But push also
implies the slang use of bird, a kilo of
coke, making ghost face with the wrist,
a reference to cooking crack. Also
notice the subtle alteration of falconer
to falconire, a play on millionaire.
Bird falconer thus implies push is
someone who's made millions via drugs.
The third and final layer continues the
previous Saudi reference as falcons are
a status symbol there and are incredibly
popular among Saudi royalty. For more
clips breakdowns just like this, check
out my new episode dissecting the 10
best bars from Let God Sort Him